Subtitle Provide by dramacool.in Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.in [Admin.@YNG]
CHO BYEONG-KYU
تشو بيونغ كيو
RYEO UN
ريو أون
JEONG JAE-KWANG
جونغ جاي كوانغ
JUNG YONG-JU
جونغ يونغ جو
CRINGY ROMANCE
رومانسية محرجة
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION
هذه الدراما هي عمل خيالي
ANY RESEMBLANCE TO ACTUAL PERSONS, EVENTS, OR BACKGROUNDS IS PURELY COINCIDENTAL
أي تشابه مع الأشخاص أو الأحداث أو الخلفيات الفعلية هو محض صدفة
ALL GUIDELINES REGARDING THE USE OF CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
جميع الإرشادات المتعلقة باستخدام الممثلين الأطفال والحيوانات
WERE STRICTLY FOLLOWED DURING FILMING
لقد تم اتباعهم بدقة أثناء التصوير
Can I ask you something?
هل يمكننى ان اسألك شيئا؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Am I your first?
هل أنا الأول لك؟
Ju-yeon!
جو يون!
So Ju-yeon!
إنها جو يون!
- I'll go this way. - Thank you.
- سأذهب من هنا. - شكرا لك.
Ju-yeon! Where are you?
جو يون! أين أنت؟
Why can't I get reception?
لماذا لا أستطيع الحصول على الاستقبال؟
Ju-yeon!
جو يون!
So Ju-yeon!
إنها جو يون!
It's working.
إنه يعمل.
Ju-yeon!
جو يون!
So Ju-yeon!
إنها جو يون!
Answer me if you're there!
أجبني إذا كنت هناك!
Ju-yeon!
جو يون!
So Ju-yeon!
إنها جو يون!
Sir!
سيد!
Help me!
ساعدني!
Help! Please help!
مساعدة! من فضلك ساعدني!
Jun-seok, are you all right?
جون سوك، هل أنت بخير؟
- Jun-seok. - Jun-seok!
- جون سوك. - جون سوك!
Noh Jun-seok!
نو جون سوك!
Jun-seok!
جون سوك!
Ju-yeon? Ju-yeon!
جو يون؟ جو يون!
Ju-yeon!
جو يون!
- Jun-seok! - Be careful!
- جون سوك! - كن حذرا!
Jun-seok!
جون سوك!
- Oh, my gosh. - I'll go find some rope.
- يا إلهي. - سأذهب للبحث عن بعض الحبال.
- Don't come any closer! - Wait.
- لا تقترب أكثر! - انتظر.
Stay there.
ابقى هناك.
- Jun-seok, grab my hand. - Have you lost your mind?
- جون سوك، أمسك يدي. - هل فقدت عقلك؟
No, have you lost your mind?
لا هل فقدت عقلك؟
- Grab my hand! - Listen to me!
- امسك يدي! - استمع لي!
Sir!
سيد!
Hey! Oh, no.
مهلا! أوه، لا.
Jun-seok, grab my hand.
جون سوك، امسك يدي.
Listen to me. Grab my hand...
استمع لي. امسك بيدي.
Help!
يساعد!
Sir!
سيد!
Ju-yeon.
جو يون.
The shirt you got me is completely ruined.
القميص الذي أهديتني إياه مدمر تماما.
Is that what you're worried about right now?
هل هذا ما يقلقك الآن؟
Sir!
سيد!
Ju-yeon.
جو يون.
If anything ever happens to me,
إذا حدث لي أي شيء،
will you break the news to my dad and comfort him?
هل ستخبر والدي بالخبر وتواسيه؟
Nothing's going to happen to you!
لن يحدث لك شيء!
I'm not going to deliver any news.
لن أقدم أي أخبار.
You tell him yourself!
أنت تقول له بنفسك!
And stop crying because of Gyu-cheol!
وتوقف عن البكاء بسبب جيو تشول!
When you cry because of him,
عندما تبكي بسببه،
it breaks my heart.
إنه يحطم قلبي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Jun-seok, no.
جون سوك، لا.
No!
لا!
No.
لا.
Are you all right? You're not hurt?
هل انت بخير؟ لم تصب بأذى؟
Hey, the cliff wasn't that high.
مهلا، المنحدر لم يكن مرتفعا إلى هذا الحد.
Yes, it was. It was pretty dangerous.
نعم، كان الأمر كذلك. كان خطيرًا جدًا.
Try getting up.
حاول النهوض.
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
You're not all right.
أنت لست بخير.
It hurts, doesn't it?
إنه يؤلمني، أليس كذلك؟
- Is it bad? - No, it doesn't hurt.
- هل هو سيء؟ - لا، لا يؤلم.
It's all good. You're safe now.
كل شيء على ما يرام. أنت بأمان الآن.
You're going to be all right.
سوف تكون بخير.
CRINGY ROMANCE
رومانسية محرجة
It's all going to be okay.
كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام.
Min-gi.
مين جي.
Min-gi?
مين جي؟
Are you crying?
هل انت تبكي؟
Why are you crying?
لماذا تبكي؟
You're crying. What's the matter?
أنت تبكي. ما الأمر؟
Why are you crying so much?
لماذا تبكي كثيرا؟
You don't like me anymore?
هل لم تعد تحبني بعد الآن؟
No.
لا.
That's not it.
هذا ليس هو.
I knew...
لقد عرفت...
that I could never be...
أنني لن أستطيع أن أكون... أبدًا
your first.
اول مرة لك.
And I understand.
وأنا أفهم.
But strangely, it makes me so upset.
ولكن الغريب أن هذا الأمر يجعلني منزعجًا جدًا.
And if I...
وإذا أنا...
had been born before you,
لقد ولدوا قبلك،
met you first,
التقيت بك أولاً
and like you first, it would have been fine.
ومثلك أولاً، كان الأمر ليكون على ما يرام.
You know... Since we were little kids.
هل تعلم... منذ أن كنا أطفالًا صغارًا.
But there's nothing I can do about that.
ولكن ليس هناك شيء يمكنني فعله حيال ذلك.
Right?
يمين؟
I still like you, though.
لا أزال أحبك، رغم ذلك.
I still like you.
لا أزال أحبك.
I like you so much.
أحبك جداً جداً.
So, why do I keep crying like an idiot?
إذن لماذا أستمر في البكاء كالأحمق؟
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
It's okay, Min-gi.
لا بأس، مين جي.
- This sucks. - Min-gi.
- هذا يمتص. - مين جي.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
It's so painful!
إنه مؤلم للغاية!
My heart aches.
قلبي يؤلمني.
Are you sure about this?
هل أنت متأكد من هذا؟
Bye.
الوداع.
So, Min-gi and his girlfriend are
لذا، مين جي وصديقته هما
in your room?
في غرفتك؟
Yes. I can just find a PC café to sleep in.
نعم. أستطيع ببساطة العثور على مقهى كمبيوتر للنوم فيه.
You can't go to a PC café looking like that.
لا يمكنك الذهاب إلى مقهى كمبيوتر وأنت تبدو بهذا الشكل.
It's fine.
إنه بخير.
- Come with me. - But...
- تعال معي. - لكن...
But I'm fine.
ولكنني بخير.
I'm telling you. It's okay.
أنا أقول لك، لا بأس.
- Does it sting? - Yes.
- هل يلسع؟ - نعم.
- Oh, no. - Be gentle.
- أوه لا. - كن لطيفا.
The wound is too deep.
الجرح عميق جداً
- Does it hurt? - Well...
- هل يؤلمك؟ - حسنًا...
What if you get a scar?
ماذا لو حصلت على ندبة؟
Stop moving. It's not dry yet.
توقف عن الحركة. لم يجف بعد.
What?
ماذا؟
I heard that you knew
سمعت أنك تعرف
Gyu-cheol was cheating on me.
كان جيو تشول يخونني.
What?
ماذا؟
- Right. - I'm so disappointed in you.
- صحيح. - أنا أشعر بخيبة أمل كبيرة فيك.
Shouldn't I matter more to you than Gyu-cheol does?
ألا ينبغي أن أكون أكثر أهمية بالنسبة لك من جيو تشول؟
Sorry.
آسف.
It's too late for that.
لقد فات الأوان لذلك.
Let me see that.
دعني أرى ذلك.
Done.
منتهي.
- Does it still hurt? - No.
- هل لا زال يؤلمني؟ - لا.
I'm worried you'll get a scar.
أنا قلق من أنك سوف تحصل على ندبة.
Get some sleep.
احصل على بعض النوم.
It's okay. We'll try again next time.
لا بأس. سنحاول مرة أخرى في المرة القادمة.
I'm usually not like this.
أنا عادة لا أكون مثل هذا.
It's because it's your first time.
لأنها المرة الأولى لك.
I'm sure we can do it next time.
أنا متأكد من أننا سنتمكن من فعل ذلك في المرة القادمة.
Are you telling me...
هل تقول لي...
you couldn't do it?
لم تستطيع فعل ذلك؟
You're so frustrating.
أنت محبط للغاية.
- Gosh. - That's enough.
- يا إلهي - هذا يكفي.
But he's a man.
ولكنه رجل.
I'm sure he feels worse.
أنا متأكد من أنه يشعر بالأسوأ.
Hey, it's all right. You can get it treated at a clinic.
لا بأس، يمكنكِ علاجه في عيادة.
You're meaner than him, dude.
أنت أكثر قسوة منه، يا صديقي.
It's fine. We'll play video games to forget about it.
لا بأس. سنلعب ألعاب الفيديو لننسى الأمر.
By the way, where's Jun-seok?
بالمناسبة، أين جون سوك؟
I thought hard about it,
لقد فكرت في الأمر جيدا،
and I think it's the smoking.
وأعتقد أن السبب هو التدخين.
See? It looks so limp.
أرأيت؟ يبدو مترهلًا جدًا.
You guys should quit too.
ينبغي عليكم أن تستقيلوا أيضاً.
Good. You'll be strong now.
حسنًا، ستكون قويًا الآن.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Ju-yeon!
جو يون!
I'm home!
أنا الوطن!
- Ju-yeon? - Yes.
-جو يون؟ -نعم.
Hey.
يا.
I told you so.
لقد قلت لك ذلك.
Of course, he's the culprit.
بالطبع، فهو الجاني.
Right?
يمين؟
What do you mean, "How did you know?"
ماذا تقصد بـ "كيف عرفت؟"
- Jun-seok. - What?
- جون سوك. - ماذا؟
- My dad's here. - Holy shit!
- والدي هنا. - يا إلهي!
Hide.
يخفي.
Listen. No parent ever suspects their child.
إستمع. لا يشك أي والد في طفله أبدًا.
That was what confused us.
هذا ما أربكنا.
Come on.
تعال.
I'm a profiler, after all. Of course, I guessed it correctly.
أنا مُحللٌّ نفسيّ، على كل حال. بالطبع، تخميني صحيح.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Yes, I know. If we ever get a chance
نعم، أعرف. إذا سنحت لنا الفرصة
to see each other at the station, we'll talk more.
لنرى بعضنا البعض في المحطة، سنتحدث أكثر.
Yes, I'll talk to you later.
نعم سأتحدث معك لاحقا.
Jeez.
يا إلهي.
Ju-yeon!
جو يون!
Is she out?
هل هي بالخارج؟
- What do we do? - Ju-yeon.
- ماذا نفعل؟ - جو يون.
Are you in there?
هل انت هناك؟
Did she leave--
هل غادرت--
Oh, my gosh.
أوه، يا إلهي.
Why didn't you answer me if you were home?
لماذا لم تجيبني عندما كنت في المنزل؟
Hey, Dad.
مرحباً يا أبي.
Why are you back so early?
لماذا عدت مبكرا؟
Something came up at the police station.
لقد حدث شيء ما في مركز الشرطة.
What are you still doing in bed? It's so late.
ماذا تفعل في السرير؟ لقد تأخر الوقت كثيرًا.
I had a fever, so I was sleeping.
لقد كنت مصابًا بالحمى، لذلك كنت نائمًا.
What? Are you feeling unwell?
ماذا؟ هل تشعر بتوعك؟
No.
لا.
It's just a cold.
إنه مجرد نزلة برد.
That's called feeling unwell!
هذا ما يسمى بالشعور بالتوعك!
How sick are you?
ما مدى مرضك؟
No, Dad. I'm totally fine. Don't mind me.
لا يا أبي، أنا بخير تمامًا. لا تهتم بي.
Stay still.
ابقى ساكنا.
Your face is all red.
وجهك أحمر بالكامل.
- Dad, just-- - Hang on.
- أبي، فقط-- - انتظر.
I think you have a fever too.
أعتقد أن لديك الحمى أيضًا.
I'm sure I'll be fine once I get some sleep.
أنا متأكد من أنني سأكون بخير عندما أحصل على بعض النوم.
Did you take medicine?
هل تناولت الدواء؟
Did you have to get sick while I was gone?
هل كان عليك أن تمرض أثناء غيابي؟
It breaks my heart.
إنه يحطم قلبي.
I'm fine. I'll recover after some sleep.
أنا بخير. سأتعافى بعد بعض النوم.
You should hurry and get to work.
ينبغي عليك الإسراع والذهاب إلى العمل.
Right.
يمين.
You'll get over your cold if you sweat it out under the covers.
سوف تتغلب على نزلة البرد إذا تعرقت تحت الأغطية.
Goodness.
الخير.
My goodness.
يا إلهي.
Your feet are a perfect copy of mine.
قدميك هي نسخة طبق الأصل من قدمي.
Just look at your broad soles.
فقط أنظر إلى باطن قدميك العريضة.
And the hairs on your big toe. Your feet look exactly like mine.
وشعر إصبع قدمك الكبير. قدمك تشبه قدمي تمامًا.
What are you doing, Dad?
ماذا تفعل يا أبي؟
Oh, boy.
أوه، يا فتى.
You grew up so fast.
لقد كبرت بسرعة كبيرة.
I was too busy
لقد كنت مشغولاً جداً
to realize how big your feet have gotten.
لتدرك مدى حجم قدميك.
Boy.
ولد.
Oh, gosh.
يا إلهي.
Even the funky smell of your feet.
حتى رائحة قدميك الكريهة.
- I love it. - Dad.
-أنا أحبه. - أبي.
What are you doing? That's gross.
ماذا تفعل؟ هذا مقزز.
What do you mean by "gross?" Don't you remember?
ماذا تقصد بكلمة "مُقزز"؟ ألا تتذكر؟
When you were little, I used to come home after work
عندما كنت صغيرًا، كنت أعود إلى المنزل بعد العمل
and kiss and massage your feet every day.
وتقبيل وتدليك قدميك كل يوم.
- You don't remember? - Dad, stop.
- لا تتذكر؟ - أبي، توقف.
What was that sound?
ما كان هذا الصوت؟
Ju-yeon, you little brat.
جو يون، أيها الطفل الصغير.
Did you fart?
هل أطلقت الريح؟
Your fart stinks, Ju-yeon!
رائحتك كريهة، جو يون!
Dad, I'm sleepy.
أبي، أنا نعسان.
All right.
حسنًا.
- Stinky fart. - Dad!
- ضرطة كريهة الرائحة. - أبي!
- It stinks.
- رائحتها كريهة.
I'm sleepy.
يغلبني النعاس.
I'll leave you alone.
سأتركك وحدك.
You can come out now.
يمكنك الخروج الآن.
That was wild.
كان ذلك جامحًا.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I almost suffocated to death.
لقد كاد أن أختنق حتى الموت.
Your dad loves you so much.
والدك يحبك كثيرًا.
He does.
إنه يفعل.
You could have died if he had seen you.
كان من الممكن أن تموت لو رآك.
- Gosh. - It's so hot.
- يا إلهي. - إنه حار جدًا.
HIDEOUT BAR
بار هايد آوت
- Gi-hyeok! - Hey.
- جي هيوك! - هي.
- Did you wait long? - No, I just got here.
- هل انتظرت طويلاً؟ - لا، لقد وصلت للتو.
This is so nice.
هذا جميل جداً.
What is?
ما هو؟
You know,
أنت تعرف،
going to watch late-night movies with you after work.
سأذهب لمشاهدة الأفلام معك في وقت متأخر من الليل بعد العمل.
Things like that.
أشياء مثل ذلك.
You're hungry, right? Why don't we grab something to eat?
أنت جائع، صحيح؟ لمَ لا نأكل شيئًا؟
Let's get hot dogs at the movies.
دعونا نحصل على الكلاب الساخنة في السينما.
Now, I'm into eating hot dogs at the movie theater.
الآن، أنا أحب أكل النقانق الساخنة في صالة السينما.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Taxi!
تاكسي!
- Come on. - Okay.
- هيا. - حسنًا.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
- Hello.
- مرحبا.
Get in.
أدخل.
Right.
يمين.
Gi-hyeok.
إنهم هيوك.
Why didn't you tell me you had such a pretty friend?
لماذا لم تخبرني أن لديك صديقًا جميلًا؟
You don't tell people about me, do you?
أنت لا تخبر الناس عني، أليس كذلك؟
No, it's not like that.
لا، ليس الأمر كذلك.
Hey.
يا.
Can I ask you
هل يمكنني أن أسألك
what your name is?
ما اسمك؟
You don't have to use the honorifics, ma'am.
لا يتوجب عليك استخدام الألقاب الشرفية، سيدتي.
But...
لكن...
we've only just met.
لقد التقينا للتو.
Should I drop the honorifics?
هل يجب علي أن أسقط الألقاب؟
I'm Hui-seon. Choi Hui-seon.
أنا هوي سون. تشوي هوي سون.
Choi Hui-seon? What a pretty name you have.
تشوي هوي سون؟ ما أجمل اسمك.
Do you mind
هل تمانع
if I call you Mother?
إذا ناديتك أمي؟
Of course. If we get closer,
بالطبع. إذا اقتربنا،
you can even call me your sister
يمكنك حتى أن تناديني بأختك
or your mom, even.
أو حتى والدتك.
I'm sorry?
أنا آسف؟
You can call me whatever you want.
يمكنك أن تناديني بأي اسم تريد.
- Come on, Mom. - What?
- هيا يا أمي. - ماذا؟
It's better than "Auntie." I hate it when your friends call me that.
إنه أفضل من "العمة". أكره عندما يناديني أصدقاؤك بذلك.
You're making her uncomfortable.
أنت تجعلها غير مرتاحة.
What do you mean? I'd love to call her my mom.
ماذا تقصد؟ أود أن أسميها أمي.
Right? I don't make you uncomfortable, do I?
صحيح؟ أنا لا أجعلك تشعر بعدم الارتياح، أليس كذلك؟
Not at all.
مُطْلَقاً.
See?
يرى؟
Hui-seon, your mom must be so proud
هوي سون، يجب أن تكون والدتك فخورة جدًا
to have such a friendly daughter.
أن يكون لدي ابنة ودودة مثلك.
I can tell that you grew up in a loving environment.
أستطيع أن أقول أنك نشأت في بيئة محبة.
I love your smile,
أنا أحب ابتسامتك،
and you have such an affectionate tone.
ولديك مثل هذه النبرة العاطفية.
Your parents must be so proud. Am I right?
لا بد أن والديك فخوران جدًا. هل أنا على حق؟
Yes.
نعم.
- Mom. - Yes?
- أمي. - نعم؟
We're almost there. You can drop us off there.
لقد اقتربنا. يمكنك توصيلنا إلى هناك.
Over there? Yes, I'll drop you off there.
هناك؟ نعم، سأوصلك إلى هناك.
CINEMA TOWN
مدينة السينما
Here we are.
نحن هنا.
- Thanks, Mom. - Thank you!
- شكرا أمي. - شكرا لك!
Take care.
يعتني.
Visit our house when you're free next time.
قم بزيارة منزلنا عندما تكون متاحًا في المرة القادمة.
I'll cook for you.
سأطبخ لك.
Mom, stop making her uncomfortable.
أمي، توقفي عن إزعاجها.
What's so uncomfortable with cooking food for my son's friend? Am I right?
ما المزعج في طهي الطعام لصديق ابني؟ أليس كذلك؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
We're late. You should go.
لقد تأخرنا، يجب عليك الذهاب.
All right.
حسنًا.
- Have fun! - Take care.
- استمتع! - اعتني بنفسك.
- Okay. - Bye.
-حسنا. - وداعا.
I can't believe this.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق هذا.
Why did it have to be my mom's taxi?
لماذا كان لابد أن تكون سيارة أجرة أمي؟
I'm sorry if it was uncomfortable.
أنا آسف إذا كان الأمر غير مريح.
Do I really look like that?
هل أبدو حقا هكذا؟
What?
ماذا؟
Does it look like I was raised in a loving environment?
هل يبدو الأمر وكأنني نشأت في بيئة محبة؟
What?
ماذا؟
So far, people have only told me
حتى الآن، أخبرني الناس فقط
that I had a troubled look
لقد كان لدي مظهر مضطرب
with a shadow on my face.
مع ظل على وجهي.
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Who said that to you? Who?
من قال لك ذلك؟ من؟
Let's get going.
دعونا ننطلق.
Okay.
تمام.
Jun-seok.
جون سوك.
Gyu-cheol cheated on me.
لقد خانني جيو تشول.
Where are you now?
أين أنت الآن؟
Okay. I'm on my way there.
حسنًا، أنا في طريقي إلى هناك.
Come on. Stop crying.
هيا، توقف عن البكاء.
Now, Ms. Yun Seol-ha,
الآن، السيدة يون سول ها،
which do you value more? Your career or your personal life?
أيهما تُقدّر أكثر؟ حياتك المهنية أم حياتك الشخصية؟
I value my career more.
أقدر مسيرتي المهنية أكثر.
Do you really?
هل حقا؟
- Why? - So, when we're on a date,
- لماذا؟ - إذن، عندما نكون في موعد،
you're going to leave me if something comes up?
هل ستتركني إذا حدث شيء ما؟
Min-gi, this is supposed to be a job interview.
مين جي، من المفترض أن تكون هذه مقابلة عمل.
Oh, you're right.
أوه، أنت على حق.
- Here you go. - Calm down.
- تفضل. - اهدأ.
- Thank you. - That looks tasty. Thank you.
- شكرًا لك. - يبدو لذيذًا. شكرًا لك.
Why? Did she say no?
لماذا؟ هل قالت لا؟
She has plans that day.
لديها خطط لهذا اليوم.
Really? That's bad news.
حقا؟ هذه أخبار سيئة.
Are you sure you'll be fine on your own?
هل أنت متأكد من أنك ستكون بخير بمفردك؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Are you trying to find someone to cover for you on that day?
هل تحاول العثور على شخص ليغطيك في ذلك اليوم؟
- I'll fill in for you. - Seriously?
- سأقوم بملئ المكان نيابة عنك. - بجدية؟
You're free that day?
هل أنت حر في ذلك اليوم؟
What's the point of having a boyfriend?
ما الفائدة من وجود صديق؟
You can always ask me if you need to move heavy things.
يمكنك دائمًا أن تسألني إذا كنت بحاجة إلى نقل أشياء ثقيلة.
I'm stronger than I look.
أنا أقوى مما أبدو.
See?
يرى؟
Min-gi just knows what to say.
مين جي يعرف فقط ما يجب أن يقوله.
Give me a kiss.
أعطني قبلة.
- Come on. - You're a lifesaver. Thanks, Min-gi.
- هيا. - أنت منقذ حياة. شكرًا، مين جي.
Baby, don't worry a thing about that. Just focus on the interview.
يا حبيبتي، لا تقلقي بشأن هذا الأمر. ركزي فقط على المقابلة.
- All right, honey? - Yes, honey.
- بخير يا عزيزتي؟ - نعم يا عزيزتي.
You can leave us alone now. I need to practice for my interview.
يمكنك تركنا وشأننا الآن. أحتاج للتدرب على المقابلة.
All right. We don't have time to joke around.
حسناً، ليس لدينا وقت للمزاح.
- Okay. - Moving on to the next question.
-حسنًا. - ننتقل إلى السؤال التالي.
What has been the most difficult challenge in your life,
ما هو التحدي الأصعب الذي واجهته في حياتك؟
and how did you overcome it?
وكيف تغلبت عليها؟
Last night?
ليلة أمس؟
Min-gi, wait!
مين جي، انتظر!
I'm joking!
أنا أمزح!
I have to stop here, right?
يجب أن أتوقف هنا، أليس كذلك؟
- Yes. And then... - I lock it here.
- نعم. وبعد ذلك... - سأقفله هنا.
- Okay. I got it. - Right here.
- حسنًا، فهمت. - هنا.
- What about my legs? Just one foot? - Forward.
- ماذا عن ساقيّ؟ قدم واحدة فقط؟ - إلى الأمام.
- Like that. And do this. - Okay.
- هكذا. وافعل هذا. - حسنًا.
Oh, right. I always forget.
أوه، صحيح. أنا دائمًا أنسى.
- Right? - Why do I keep forgetting?
- صحيح؟ - لماذا أظل أنسى؟
I just can't get this right.
لا أستطيع الحصول على هذا الحق.
I just can't.
لا استطيع ذلك.
Hey, Yeon-jeong.
مهلا، يون جونغ.
Chae-yeong!
تشاي يونغ!
What's up with you, girl?
ماذا بك يا فتاة؟
- Do you go to clubs together? - What?
- هل تذهبون إلى النوادي معًا؟ - ماذا؟
It's just that you haven't been around.
إن الأمر فقط هو أنك لم تكن موجودًا.
Stay out of this.
ابقى خارج هذا .
You're drunk, aren't you? That's cute.
أنت سكران، أليس كذلك؟ هذا لطيف.
So, what's up? You never call me.
إذن، ما الأمر؟ أنت لا تتصل بي أبدًا.
I called you, but it was a non-working number.
لقد اتصلت بك، لكنه كان رقمًا غير عامل.
Did you get a new phone?
هل حصلت على هاتف جديد؟
Yes, it's been some time since I changed my phone.
نعم لقد مر بعض الوقت منذ أن قمت بتغيير هاتفي.
Didn't I tell you my new number?
ألم أخبرك برقمي الجديد؟
Sorry. I must have forgotten. I'll tell you now.
آسف. يبدو أنني نسيت. سأخبرك الآن.
Oh, that's why you never texted back.
أوه، هذا هو السبب في أنك لم ترسل رسالة نصية أبدًا.
I'll save it.
سأحفظه.
- Use one leg only. - You're really good.
- استخدم ساقًا واحدة فقط. - أنت جيد حقًا.
Why can't I do it naturally?
لماذا لا أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك بشكل طبيعي؟
- Gosh. Just my wrists? - And turn your wrists.
يا إلهي. معصميّ فقط؟ - وأدر معصميك.
One and two.
واحد و اثنان.
- One and two. - And point.
- واحد واثنين. - ونقطة.
Yeon-jeong.
يون جونغ.
You're doing it again.
أنت تفعل ذلك مرة أخرى.
Your face when you dance.
وجهك عندما ترقص.
Why do you do this?
لماذا تفعل هذا؟
That's so weird.
هذا غريب جدًا.
It's so cringe. Don't you agree, Gwang-jae?
إنه أمرٌ مُحرجٌ جدًا. ألا توافقني الرأي يا غوانغ جاي؟
It's cringe, right?
إنه أمر محرج، أليس كذلك؟
But you're supposed to smile a bit when you're locking, so...
لكن من المفترض أن تبتسم قليلاً عندما تقوم بالإغلاق، لذا...
I know that.
وأنا أعلم ذلك.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
That's not what I mean.
هذا ليس ما أقصده.
I'm saying it doesn't suit her.
أنا أقول أنه لا يناسبها.
It's so cringeworthy.
إنه أمر محرج للغاية.
She always has that depressed look on her face.
إنها دائما لديها نظرة الاكتئاب على وجهها.
Sorry, Yeon-jeong.
آسف، يون جونغ.
I'm not trying to say that you're ugly.
أنا لا أحاول أن أقول أنك قبيح.
That's definitely not true.
هذا ليس صحيحا بالتأكيد.
You don't get it.
أنت لا تفهم ذلك.
You should have seen her when she was in high school.
كان ينبغي عليك رؤيتها عندما كانت في المدرسة الثانوية.
Her face was depressed as heck.
كان وجهها مكتئبا للغاية.
Oh, I get it now. You tend to do that to close friends.
أوه، فهمت الآن. عادةً ما تفعل ذلك مع أصدقائك المقربين.
I know what that's like. But you know what?
أعرف ذلك. لكن هل تعلم؟
From an objective point of view, it's not weird at all.
من وجهة نظر موضوعية، فالأمر ليس غريباً على الإطلاق.
You look so cool.
أنت تبدو رائعاً جداً.
Yes, I'm the asshole.
نعم، أنا الأحمق.
- Come on. Let's just drink. - Go away.
- هيا، لنشرب فقط. - ابتعد.
Yeon-jeong, do that little dance again.
يون جونغ، قومي بهذه الرقصة الصغيرة مرة أخرى.
You know? Like this.
هل تعلم؟ مثل هذا.
Chae-yeong, you're drunk.
تشاي يونغ، أنت في حالة سكر.
Oh, please. Do that little dance again. Just once.
أرجوك، كرر هذه الرقصة الصغيرة مرة أخرى. ولو لمرة واحدة.
- Do it. - Kim Chae-yeong.
- افعلها. - كيم تشاي يونغ.
You're being really rude to her.
أنت وقح جدًا معها.
I don't believe this.
انا لا اصدق هذا.
Why do you care?
لماذا تهتم؟
Just go home. You're being obnoxious.
فقط اذهب إلى المنزل، أنت مزعج.
Moron.
المغفل.
I wouldn't stay, even if you begged me.
لن أبقى، حتى لو توسلت إلي.
You're always chasing after anyone, anyway.
أنت دائمًا تطارد أي شخص، على أي حال.
Did you wash your hair with beer or something?
هل غسلت شعرك بالبيرة أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
You look freaking lame. Do you know that?
تبدو ضعيفًا جدًا. هل تعلم ذلك؟
- Chae-yeong. - Don't touch me!
- تشاي يونغ. - لا تلمسني!
Damn it. Don't get cocky with me.
يا إلهي، لا تكن مغرورًا معي.
Hey, Skidmark.
مرحبًا، سكيدمارك.
Did you honestly think I was your friend just because I hung out with you?
هل كنت تعتقد حقًا أنني صديقك لمجرد أنني كنت معك؟
- That's enough. - Get off me.
- هذا يكفي. - ابتعد عني.
Not once did I ever consider you a friend.
لم أعتبرك صديقًا أبدًا.
Are you being serious?
هل انت جاد؟
Get your hands off me!
ابعد يديك عني!
Get out of my face.
اغرب عن وجهي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
It's my fault.
إنه خطئي.
Does it look like
هل يبدو مثل
I washed it with beer to you too?
غسلته بالبيرة لك أيضا؟
What?
ماذا؟
My hair, I mean.
شعري، أعني.
No, not at all.
لا، على الإطلاق.
That's a trend in the US.
وهذا هو الاتجاه في الولايات المتحدة.
I knew you'd know!
لقد عرفت أنك ستعرف!
Of course, I do. Eminem also has that hair color.
بالطبع، لديّ. إيمينيم أيضًا لديه هذا اللون من الشعر.
Tell me about it!
أخبرني عن ذلك!
It kept gnawing at me
لقد ظل يقضمني
after she said it looked like I washed it with beer.
بعد أن قالت أنها تبدو وكأنني غسلتها بالبيرة.
Seriously.
بجد.
It's an American style.
إنه أسلوب أمريكي.
She doesn't get it.
إنها لا تفهم ذلك.
- Hold on. - What?
-انتظر. -ماذا؟
That's smart.
هذا ذكي.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
I listened to that CD by... Was it Sisoo?
لقد استمعت إلى هذا القرص المضغوط بواسطة... هل كان سيسو؟
It was so good.
لقد كان جيدا جدا.
- Do you mean Sisqó? - Yes, Sisqó.
- هل تقصد سيسكو؟ - نعم، سيسكو.
- His songs are so good, right? - How did you know about him?
- أغانيه جميلة جدًا، أليس كذلك؟ - كيف عرفت عنه؟
- A friend from my dance club told me. - Really?
- أخبرني أحد أصدقائي من نادي الرقص الخاص بي. - حقًا؟
Stop moving. It's not dry yet.
توقف عن الحركة. لم يجف بعد.
You have big hands.
لديك أيدي كبيرة.
I'm telling you!
انا اخبرك!
Don't just be nice to us when we're here. Answer our calls once in a while.
لا تكتفِ باللطف معنا أثناء وجودنا هنا، بل أجب على اتصالاتنا من حين لآخر.
- He's right. - That way, I can buy some drinks here.
- إنه على حق. - بهذه الطريقة، أستطيع شراء بعض المشروبات هنا.
- Or we can all go outside and drink. - Yes.
- أو يمكننا جميعًا أن نخرج ونشرب. - نعم.
- We should drink soju outside. - Yes, just today.
- ينبغي لنا أن نشرب السوجو في الخارج. - نعم، اليوم فقط.
Hey, what are you thinking about?
مهلا، ماذا تفكر فيه؟
- Shoot. - Oh, my gosh.
- أطلق النار. - أوه، يا إلهي.
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
هل انت بخير؟ هل انت مصاب؟
- Go to the back. - Gosh, what the hell?
- اذهب إلى الخلف. - يا إلهي، ماذا بحق الجحيم؟
- Damn it, this hurts. - Oh, dear.
- اللعنة، هذا يؤلمني. - أوه، عزيزي.
- Damn it. - I'm terribly sorry.
- اللعنة. - أنا آسف للغاية.
- Gosh. - Let me see that.
- يا إلهي. - دعني أرى ذلك.
- Are you okay? - I'm fine.
- هل أنت بخير؟ - أنا بخير.
She was feeling unwell today,
لقد كانت تشعر بتوعك اليوم،
but I made her come to work.
لكنني جعلتها تأتي إلى العمل.
- She should have taken a day off, then. - I know!
- كان ينبغي لها أن تأخذ يوم إجازة إذن. - أعلم!
It's all my fault. I'm so sorry.
إنه خطئي بالكامل. أنا آسف جدًا.
You look amazing in a suit!
تبدو مذهلة في البدلة!
It feels a bit awkward wearing a suit again after so long.
أشعر بالحرج قليلاً عند ارتداء بدلة مرة أخرى بعد فترة طويلة.
How do I look? Do you like it?
كيف أبدو؟ هل يعجبك؟
I love it.
أنا أحبه.
This is your type, isn't it?
هذا هو نوعك، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
No, I just meant that you looked good in it.
لا، كنت أقصد فقط أنك تبدو جيدًا فيه.
Oh, right. Let's go to this...
حسنًا، لننتقل إلى هذا...
after your interview today.
بعد مقابلتك اليوم.
LOTTE WORLD, ALL-DAY PASS
لوت وورلد، تذكرة دخول ليوم كامل
Wait.
انتظر.
You remembered?
هل تذكرت؟
- What do you mean? - What's this about?
- ماذا تقصد؟ - ما هذا؟
- I love you so much, Min-gi. - What is it?
- أنا أحبك كثيرًا، مين جي. - ما الأمر؟
I told him that I had never been to Lotte World since high school.
أخبرته أنني لم أذهب إلى Lotte World أبدًا منذ المدرسة الثانوية.
How attentive you are.
كم أنت منتبه.
Anyway, let's go there after your interview.
على أية حال، دعنا نذهب إلى هناك بعد المقابلة.
All right. I'm going to kill it.
حسناً، سأقتله.
- You've got this. - I'm running late. Bye.
- أنت قادر على ذلك. - أنا متأخر. مع السلامة.
- You can do it! - I can do it.
- يمكنك فعل ذلك! - أنا أستطيع فعل ذلك.
- Good luck. - You got this.
- حظا سعيدا. - لقد حصلت على هذا.
I'll see you later.
سوف أراك لاحقا.
Why am I so nervous?
لماذا أنا متوترة جداً؟
Seol-ha!
أرسلها!
Yes?
نعم؟
Good luck!
حظ سعيد!
I'll see you tonight.
سوف أراك الليلة.
- Ms. Yun Seol-ha? - Yes.
- السيدة يون سول ها؟ - نعم.
You were a team leader at YT Company.
لقد كنت قائد فريق في شركة YT.
- That's impressive.
- هذا مثير للإعجاب.
The head of a team at the age of 26.
رئيس فريق في عمر 26 عامًا.
Yes. I had worked there as an intern...
نعم. لقد عملت هناك كمتدرب.
since I was a college sophomore.
منذ أن كنت طالبة في السنة الثانية بالجامعة.
You must be competent.
يجب أن تكون كفؤًا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Yeo-jin, do you need me to do anything else before I leave?
يو جين، هل تريدين مني أن أفعل أي شيء آخر قبل أن أغادر؟
No, you've done all you could. Thanks for today. Get ready to leave.
لا، لقد بذلتَ كل ما في وسعك. شكرًا لك على هذا اليوم. استعد للمغادرة.
Are you going straight to Lotte World?
هل أنت ذاهب مباشرة إلى Lotte World؟
Yes, I'm supposed to meet her at the front gate.
نعم، من المفترض أن أقابلها عند البوابة الأمامية.
She must be so excited.
لا بد أنها متحمسة جدًا.
- Hello. - Can I get a pancake?
- مرحباً. - هل يمكنني الحصول على فطيرة؟
That will be five dollars. I'll bring it to your table.
هذا سيكون خمسة دولارات. سأحضره إلى طاولتك.
- I'll get going. - Bye.
- سأذهب. - وداعا.
Wait. You can't park there.
انتظر. لا يمكنك ركن سيارتك هناك.
Sir, you can't park there.
سيدي، لا يمكنك ركن سيارتك هناك.
I just need to bring this in.
كل ما أحتاجه هو إحضار هذا.
Oh, hi.
أوه، مرحباً.
I'll take that.
سوف آخذ ذلك.
These are Brazilian coffee beans.
هذه حبوب البن البرازيلية.
- You can give them to the owner. - You were
- يمكنك إعطائهم للمالك. - كنت
Seol-ha's supervisor at her previous company, right?
مشرفة سول ها في شركتها السابقة، أليس كذلك؟
Pardon? What...
عفواً؟ ماذا...
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
- At the soju bar, right? - Yes.
- في بار السوجو، أليس كذلك؟ - نعم.
- You were with Seol-ha. - I was.
- كنت مع سول ها. - كنت.
- It's nice to see you. - Hello.
- يسعدني رؤيتك. - مرحباً.
Didn't she come to work today?
ألم تأت إلى العمل اليوم؟
Oh, she's at a job interview.
أوه، إنها في مقابلة عمل.
Oh, an interview?
أوه، مقابلة؟
Do you know which company it is?
هل تعرف أي شركة هي؟
It was "Brill" something.
لقد كان "بريل" شيئا ما.
Is it Brilliant Communications?
هل هي اتصالات رائعة؟
Oh, yes. That's the one.
أوه نعم. هذا هو.
But...
لكن...
how do you know her?
كيف تعرفها؟
I'm her boyfriend.
أنا صديقها.
- Boyfriend? - Yes.
- صديق؟ - نعم.
Like a lover?
مثل الحبيب؟
Yes, a lover.
نعم حبيب.
You were also a part of the Zeus Card project?
هل كنت أيضًا جزءًا من مشروع بطاقة زيوس؟
Yes.
نعم.
Did you know that our company also entered a bid?
هل تعلم أن شركتنا قدمت عرضًا أيضًا؟
- Yes. - We lost that
- نعم. - لقد فقدنا ذلك
in the final stage, didn't we?
في المرحلة النهائية، أليس كذلك؟
YT Company pulled some strings, and we got totally screwed.
لقد قامت شركة YT بسحب بعض الخيوط، وتعرضنا لمشكلة كبيرة.
Your recent submission for Zeus Card went through.
لقد تم قبول طلبك الأخير لبطاقة زيوس .
Didn't you say the feedback in the second round wasn't that positive?
ألم تقل أن ردود الفعل في الجولة الثانية لم تكن إيجابية؟
I talked to their CEO while playing golf.
لقد تحدثت مع الرئيس التنفيذي للشركة أثناء لعب الجولف.
And they actually accepted it?
وهل قبلوا ذلك فعليا؟
And they actually accepted it.
وفعلا قبلوا ذلك.
Anyway, once this goes through,
على أية حال، بمجرد حدوث هذا،
you're becoming a team leader.
لقد أصبحت قائدًا للفريق.
I can't be a team leader already.
لا أستطيع أن أكون قائدًا للفريق بالفعل.
- I've just joined the company. - It's my decision since I'm the boss.
- لقد انضممت للتو إلى الشركة. - هذا قراري لأنني المدير.
But I said I'd handle it with my abilities.
ولكنني قلت أنني سأتعامل مع الأمر بقدراتي.
Just get ready to pick up the tab for being a team leader.
فقط كن مستعدًا لتحمل تكلفة كونك قائدًا للفريق.
Mika World, Lyon Croissant, Sangpyeong Bank...
ميكا وورلد، ليون كرواسون، بنك سانجبيونج...
You took part in all of their advertising campaigns?
هل شاركت في جميع حملاتهم الإعلانية؟
I did.
فعلتُ.
Can you elaborate on your roles in those campaigns?
هل يمكنك توضيح دورك في هذه الحملات؟
Well, I merely participated in them
حسنًا، لقد شاركت فيها فقط
as a member of the team.
كعضو في الفريق.
How did you become a team leader if that was all you did?
كيف أصبحت قائدًا للفريق إذا كان هذا كل ما تفعله؟
At the age of 26, at that.
في سن الـ26، في ذلك الوقت.
Well...
حسنًا...
This industry is smaller than you think. Word gets around fast.
هذه الصناعة أصغر مما تظن. ينتشر الخبر بسرعة.
You might have been better off not listing all that experience.
ربما كان من الأفضل عدم ذكر كل تلك التجارب.
At your age, such an impressive resume
في عمرك، مثل هذه السيرة الذاتية المثيرة للإعجاب
is bound to raise some doubts.
من المؤكد أنه سيثير بعض الشكوك.
Yong-taek.
يونغ تايك.
- Hey. - Give me a moment.
- مهلا. - أعطني لحظة.
- Here you go. - Gosh.
- تفضل. - يا إلهي.
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
The coffee beans.
حبوب البن.
Oh, the beans! You didn't have to. Thank you.
يا للفاصوليا! ما كان لازم. شكرًا.
Right. I see that Seol-ha
حسنًا، أرى أن سول ها
has a boyfriend now.
لدي صديق الآن.
Yes.
نعم.
This industry is smaller than you think.
هذه الصناعة أصغر مما تظن.
Word gets around fast.
تنتشر الكلمة بسرعة.
At your age, such an impressive resume
في عمرك، مثل هذه السيرة الذاتية المثيرة للإعجاب
is bound to raise some doubts.
من المؤكد أنه سيثير بعض الشكوك.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Did the interview not go well?
هل المقابلة لم تسير بشكل جيد؟
It went well.
لقد سارت الأمور على ما يرام.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Shoot.
أطلق النار.
Hey, Yeon-jeong!
مهلا، يون جونغ!
- Hey. Why are you here so early? - Hey!
- مهلاً. لماذا أتيتَ مُبكراً؟ - مهلاً!
- Why is the line so long? - It's because of that.
- لماذا الخط طويل جدًا؟ - هذا هو السبب.
It's the club's second anniversary, so they're giving out free drinks.
إنه الذكرى السنوية الثانية للنادي، لذا فهم يقدمون المشروبات مجانًا.
I've been waiting since 4 p.m. or something.
لقد كنت أنتظر منذ الساعة الرابعة عصرًا أو شيء من هذا القبيل.
- Since 4 p.m.? - Yes.
-منذ الساعة الرابعة عصرا؟ -نعم.
My, gosh. That must have been tough.
يا إلهي، لا بد أن الأمر كان صعبًا.
Where's my ID?
أين هويتي؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
All right.
حسنًا.
- What's this? - It's a lottery ticket.
- ما هذا؟ - إنها تذكرة يانصيب.
A lottery ticket?
تذكرة يانصيب؟
- Here. - All right.
- هنا. - حسنًا.
- Thank you. - Have fun.
- شكرا لك. - استمتع.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Let's go, Seol-ha.
دعنا نذهب، سول ها.
Sorry!
آسف!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
- I'll get you some napkins. - That's fine.
- سأحضر لك بعض المناديل. - لا بأس.
- I'll just go to the restroom. - But...
- سأذهب إلى الحمام. - لكن...
the napkins--
المناديل--
Okay.
تمام.
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
You know what to do.
أنت تعرف ماذا تفعل.
Hold it.
إمسكها.
That looks good.
هذا يبدو جيدا.
- Cheers!
- هتاف!
Should we get some more shots?
هل يجب علينا الحصول على المزيد من اللقطات؟
Let's take a short break. We've been drinking too fast.
لنأخذ استراحة قصيرة. لقد شربنا بسرعة كبيرة.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
Gosh.
يا إلهي.
Right. Let's scratch this.
حسناً، لننتهي من هذا.
- The ticket. - Wait. I have some coins.
- التذكرة. - انتظر. لدي بعض العملات.
Coins? Great.
عملات معدنية؟ رائعة.
- Here. - Okay. I'll scratch mine.
- هنا. - حسنًا. سأخدش خاصتي.
- Darn it. - Gosh.
- اللعنة. - يا إلهي.
It's a dud.
إنها فاشلة.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
Try mine.
جرب لي.
Here goes nothing.
لا يوجد شيء هنا.
Oh, it's red! I see red letters!
أوه، إنه أحمر! أرى حروفًا حمراء!
We got it.
لقد حصلنا عليه.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
What?
ماذا؟
What does it say?
ماذا يقول؟
1 NIGHT AT HONGIN THEMED MOTEL
ليلة واحدة في فندق هونغين ذي الطابع الخاص
VALID FOR 2 WEEKS FROM THE WINNING DATE, 1ST PLACE: 1 NIGHT AT HONGIN THEMED MOTEL
صالحة لمدة أسبوعين من تاريخ الفوز، المركز الأول: ليلة واحدة في فندق هونغين ذي الطابع الخاص
What...
ماذا...
What kind of prize is this?
ما نوع هذه الجائزة؟
It's very...
إنه... جداً
- It's the first prize, though. - It is.
- إنها الجائزة الأولى، على أية حال. - إنها كذلك.
Where are we going?
إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
You said you wanted to go on a roller-coaster ride.
لقد قلت أنك تريد الذهاب في رحلة على متن قطار الملاهي.
But the roller coaster is that way.
لكن الأفعوانية هي في هذا الاتجاه.
What's the matter with you? Tell me.
ما بك؟ أخبرني.
Is it because I'm not having much fun?
هل هذا لأنني لا أستمتع كثيرًا؟
Min-gi, today has actually been...
مين جي، اليوم كان في الواقع...
It was a bit--
لقد كان قليلا--
You used to date him, right?
لقد كنت تواعدينه، أليس كذلك؟
Why didn't you tell me the guy we met at the soju bar was your ex?
لماذا لم تخبرني أن الرجل الذي قابلناه في بار السوجو هو حبيبك السابق؟
We weren't dating at the time.
لم نكن نتواعد في ذلك الوقت.
Then, you should have called him and told him
إذن كان يجب عليك أن تتصل به وتخبره
that you got a new boyfriend after we started dating.
أنك حصلت على صديق جديد بعد أن بدأنا المواعدة.
How would I tell him when we never ran into each other?
كيف سأخبره أننا لم نلتقي أبدًا؟
You should have at least called him and told him you had a new boyfriend!
كان يجب عليك على الأقل أن تتصلي به وتخبريه أن لديك صديقًا جديدًا!
Don't get mad. I'm sorry. Okay?
لا تغضب. أنا آسف. حسنًا؟
Let's not do this here.
لا ينبغي لنا أن نفعل هذا هنا.
Not today.
ليس اليوم.
It's been too tough today. The interview was--
لقد كان الأمر صعبًا للغاية اليوم. المقابلة كانت--
Tough? What is?
صعب؟ ما هو؟
What's so tough?
ما هو الصعب جدا؟
How are you so selfish?
كيف تكون أنانيًا إلى هذه الدرجة؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
You only care about your feelings, don't you?
أنت تهتم فقط بمشاعرك، أليس كذلك؟
Do you even care how I feel?
هل تهتم بما أشعر به؟
Have I always been...
هل كنت دائما...؟
selfish around you?
أناني من حولك؟
Yes.
نعم.
I see.
أرى.
I'm sorry if I have.
أنا آسف إذا كان لدي.
I'm sorry I've been selfish.
أنا آسف لقد كنت أنانيًا.
Hui-seon, come and take a seat.
هوي سون، تعال واجلس.
Okay.
تمام.
I wired your monthly pay to your bank account.
لقد قمت بتحويل راتبك الشهري إلى حسابك البنكي.
Here. Take it.
هنا. خذها.
- What is it? - It's your severance pay.
- ما هو؟ - إنه مكافأة نهاية الخدمة الخاصة بك.
You've done well so far.
لقد قمت بعمل جيد حتى الآن.
I didn't know you gave out severance pay.
لم أكن أعلم أنك تقوم بتوزيع مكافأة نهاية الخدمة.
What are you going to do when you quit?
ماذا ستفعل عندما تستقيل؟
I'm going to find a vocational school.
سأبحث عن مدرسة مهنية.
And study for the GED.
ودراسة للحصول على شهادة GED.
Unbelievable.
لا يصدق.
Funny how you didn't care at all when I told you to do that.
من المضحك أنك لم تهتم على الإطلاق عندما طلبت منك أن تفعل ذلك.
I know, right?
أنا أوافق؟
Gi-hyeok has done the impossible. You should thank him.
لقد فعل جي هيوك المستحيل. يجب أن تشكره.
It's not entirely because of him.
ليس كليا بفضله.
I was planning on doing this someday.
لقد كنت أخطط للقيام بهذا يومًا ما.
I kept telling myself, "Someday,"
كنت أقول لنفسي "يوما ما"
and look what I've become.
وانظر ماذا أصبحت.
Just a bar hostess.
مجرد مضيفة بار.
What are you talking about? What's so wrong with what you do?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟ ما الخطأ في ما تفعله؟
Jeez.
يا إلهي.
But I had fun while I was working here.
لكنني استمتعت بوقتي أثناء عملي هنا.
There were many happy memories.
لقد كانت هناك العديد من الذكريات السعيدة.
And you were so nice to me.
وكنت لطيفا جدا معي.
Get out of here. It's getting late.
اخرج من هنا، لقد تأخر الوقت.
- Ung-cheol. - Don't.
- أونغ تشول. - لا تفعل.
- I'll take care of him. - I got it.
- سأعتني به. - حصلت عليه.
You should go to Gi-hyeok.
ينبغي عليك أن تذهب إلى جي هيوك.
- Come on. - I'm not seeing him today.
- هيا. - لن أراه اليوم.
- Ung-cheol, wake up. - Wake up.
- أونغ تشول، استيقظ. - استيقظ.
- It's time to go home. - Get up.
- حان وقت العودة إلى المنزل.
I better drop him off on my way home.
من الأفضل أن أتركه في طريقي إلى المنزل.
Stand up, Ung-cheol.
قف، أونغ تشول.
HIDEOUT BAR
بار هايد آوت
Is there anything you want?
هل هناك أي شيء تريده؟
Roses?
الورود؟
Yes. I've never gotten them before.
نعم لم أحصل عليهم من قبل.
Taxi!
تاكسي!
- I'm fine. - Get in the car.
- أنا بخير. - اركب السيارة.
- Oh, gosh. - Come on.
- يا إلهي. - هيا.
Just get in the car.
فقط ادخل إلى السيارة.
- I'll take him home. - What?
-سآخذه إلى المنزل. -ماذا؟
Good night! Bye!
تصبح على خير! مع السلامة!
Gosh, how...
يا إلهي، كيف...
How did we win this?
كيف فزنا بهذا؟
- Man. - Well,
- يا رجل. - حسنًا،
it's not such a bad place. You can rent DVDs too.
إنه مكان جيد. يمكنك استئجار أقراص DVD أيضًا.
And you can get as much ice cream as you want.
ويمكنك الحصول على كمية الآيس كريم التي تريدها.
- Seriously? - Yes.
- بجدية؟ - نعم.
Have you been there?
هل كنت هناك؟
- Why?
- لماذا؟
What do you mean, "Why?"
ماذا تقصد بـ "لماذا؟"
What do you do at a motel?
ماذا تفعل في الفندق؟
What? Are you serious?
ماذا؟ هل أنت جاد؟
So, you've done it before?
فهل فعلت ذلك من قبل؟
You said you've never had a boyfriend before.
قلت أنك لم يكن لديك صديق من قبل.
You don't have to be in a relationship to do that.
لا يلزم أن تكون في علاقة لتفعل ذلك.
I need a drink.
أحتاج إلى شراب.
You?
أنت؟
Why?
لماذا؟
You think no man would want to sleep with me?
هل تعتقد أن لا يوجد رجل يريد النوم معي؟
No, that's not what I mean! I mean...
لا، ليس هذا ما أقصده! أعني...
Let's just drink.
دعونا نشرب فقط.
Gosh.
يا إلهي.
How come you and I have the exact same mindset?
لماذا لدينا نفس العقلية بالضبط؟
It's the American Dream, you know?
إنه الحلم الأمريكي، هل تعلم؟
Honestly, I don't think
بصراحة لا أعتقد
that's a big deal.
هذه مشكلة كبيرة.
You know?
أنت تعرف؟
There's nothing wrong with sleeping with someone you're into.
لا يوجد خطأ في النوم مع شخص تحبه.
That's called being honest, right?
هذا ما يسمى بالصدق، أليس كذلك؟
You're right.
أنت على حق.
Man. Cheers.
يا رجل، هتاف.
You're a virgin, aren't you?
أنت عذراء، أليس كذلك؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Are you out of your mind?
هل أنت خارج عقلك؟
I've been with tons of girls.
لقد كنت مع الكثير من الفتيات.
- No way. - You don't believe me?
- لا يمكن. - لا تصدقني؟
I wish I could prove it to you.
أتمنى أن أستطيع إثبات ذلك لك.
Are you up?
هل انت مستيقظ؟